Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives, 1905 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2004; UA176.002; 5.0 Linear Feet
  - Events, Spring, 1989 -- 1991; UA176.002.013.00002
    - Purdue Speaker, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00010 (Box 13)
    - Panel of Speakers, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00011 (Box 13)
    - Speakers/ Tent, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00012 (Box 13)
    - back to back men with saxaphone, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00013 (Box 13)
    - Woman at Desk, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00014 (Box 13)
    - Accident, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00015 (Box 13)
    - Jills Concert, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00016 (Box 13)
    - Bio Proof, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00017; Nathalia (Box 13)
    - Woman Lecturing, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00018 (Box 13)
    - People cooking/ Man lecturing, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00019 (Box 13)
    - Men at Computer, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00020 (Box 13)
    - Men's Tennis, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00021; Tittman, Oliver (Box 13)
    - Woman in Kitchen, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00022 (Box 13)
    - Baseball, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00023; Mara (Box 13)
    - Men's Lacorsse, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00024; Staff, Ron (Box 13)
    - Softball, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00025; Karl (Box 13)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00026; Waldek (Box 13)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00027; Waldek (Box 13)
    - Masspirg, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00028; Julio (Box 13)
    - Chorale Concert, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00029; Denise (Box 13)
    - Conference on S. Asia at Fletcher + Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00030; Mara (Box 13)
    - Trustee Lunch, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00031 (Box 13)
    - Symposium, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00032; Karl (Box 13)
    - Jean Mayer + Memorial Cannon, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00033; Mara (Box 13)
    - Battle of the Bands, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00034; Karl (Box 13)
    - Children of War, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00035; Ajita (Box 13)
    - Candidates, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00036; Karl (Box 13)
    - Date Rape Panel, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00037; Karl (Box 13)
    - Extravaganza, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00038 (Box 13)
    - Gardener Museum, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00039; Shyder, Brian (Box 13)
    - Kerry Granitz, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00040; Jonathan (Box 13)
    - Growth Management Forum, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00041 (Box 13)
    - Homelessness (Panel?) / New Alliance Leader, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00042; Mara (Box 13)
    - Theta Delta Chi House/ Campus Center, 1991; UA176.002.013.00002.00043; Mara (Box 13)
    - Max Croek, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00044; Karl (Box 13)
    - New Dorm Construction/ Eaton Café Renovation, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00045; Karl (Box 13)
    - Bruce Paley, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00046; Grover, Jon (Box 13)
    - Matt Polombo- Folk Singer, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00047; Karl (Box 13)
    - Harry Ratcliff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00048; Denise (Box 13)
    - Cement Canoe, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00049; Walden (Box 13)
    - Cigarettes+ Condoms + Wessel, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00050; Denise + Jonathan (Box 13)
    - Community Health Building, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00051; Karl (Box 13)
    - Concert, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00052; Karl (Box 13)
    - French Dude, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00053; Karl (Box 13)
    - Jean Mayer/ Senator John Kerry, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00054; Denise (Box 13)
    - Maks, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00055; Denise (Box 13)
    - Elephant, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00056; Denise (Box 13)
    - Rally, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00057; Mara (Box 13)
    - Rally, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00058; Karl (Box 13)
    - Rally, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00059; Karl (Box 13)
    - Rally, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00060; Denise (Box 13)
    - Rally, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00061; Colin (Box 13)
    - Beyond the Barricades, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00062; Jen (Box 13)
    - Senate Candidates, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00063 (Box 13)
    - Senate Cadidates, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00064; Denise (Box 13)
    - Symposium, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00065; Karl (Box 13)
    - Sherman + Feishman, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00066; Karl (Box 13)
    - June Jordan, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00067; Jen (Box 13)
    - Blood Drive, 1989; UA176.002.013.00002.00068 (Box 13)
    - Side Effects/ Jills, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00069; Karl (Box 13)
    - Mara Samann, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00070 (Box 13)
    - Panel, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00071 (Box 13)
    - Women, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00072 (Box 13)
    - Rally, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00073 (Box 13)
    - 1st Panel, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00074; Denise (Box 13)
    - Panel, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00075 (Box 13)
    - Jon Kleinschmidt, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00076 (Box 13)
    - Women's Thing, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00077 (Box 13)
    - Joe Graner, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00078; Albano, Sal (Box 13)
    - Voting + Blood Drive, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00079 (Box 13)
    - Tuftspeak, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00080; Haskell, Joel (Box 13)
    - Cement Canoe, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00081; Walden (Box 13)
    - Take Back the Night, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00082; Denise (Box 13)
    - Politics + Religion, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00083 (Box 13)
    - Evelyn Murphy Lieutenant Governer, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00084; Denise (Box 13)
    - Candle Vigil, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00085; Kischatz (Box 13)
    - Senate, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00086 (Box 13)
    - Amatz Asa-El, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00087 (Box 13)
    - Armenian Club, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00088 (Box 13)
    - Sleepout for the Homeless, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00089; Mota, Julio (Box 13)
    - Senate Meetings, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00090; Newman, Steve (Box 13)
    - Kid's Day, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00091 (Box 13)
    - Theta Chai Couch-a-Thon, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00092 (Box 13)
    - Spring Fling, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00093 (Box 13)
    - Voting, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00094 (Box 13)
    - Wynton Marsalis, 1990; UA176.002.013.00002.00095; Neuman, Steve (Box 13)
  - Events, Fall, 1990 -- 1991; UA176.002.013.00003
    - Howard Orientation, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00001 (Box 13)
    - Jon Orientation, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00002 (Box 13)
    - Howard Orientation, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00003 (Box 13)
    - Matriculation, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00004; Denise (Box 13)
    - Orientation, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00005; Jon (Box 13)
    - Prof. Winter, 1991; UA176.002.013.00003.00006; Jen (Box 13)
    - Tufts Arena, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00007; Hilary, Gayle (Box 13)
    - Construction and Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00008; Mara (Box 13)
    - Howard, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00009 (Box 13)
    - Date Rape Skit/ Prof. Feigenbaum (Math Dept.), 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00010; Riemer, Mara (Box 13)
    - Director of Dining, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00011; Miller, Liza (Box 13)
    - Convocation/ Jenny Rankin, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00012; Jon (Box 13)
    - Fluff + Cohen + Smoker, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00013; Mara (Box 13)
    - Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00014; Anderson, Christine (Box 13)
    - Senate Candidates, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00015; Zalas, Lukas (Box 13)
    - AIDS Memorial Quilt, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00016; Yudiu, Pam (Box 13)
    - Rev. Mwadime, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00017; Bigden, Jon (Box 13)
    - Stillman, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00018; Newman, Steve (Box 13)
    - Neil Hare, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00019; Hare, Neil (Box 13)
    - Links Meeting, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00020; Pescarmona, Sophia (Box 13)
    - Indian Food, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00021; Jen (Box 13)
    - Candle Light Vigil, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00022; Oliver (?) (Box 13)
    - Kid's Fair, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00023; Kaitsa (Box 13)
    - Wall of Velcro/ Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00024; Jen (Box 13)
    - Voting, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00025; Oliver (Box 13)
    - Food Drive/ Elephant Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00026; Julio (Box 13)
    - Jazz Band (Bing Spar Bidu), 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00027; Newman, Steve (Box 13)
    - Jose Masso, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00028; Sofia (Box 13)
    - Black Theater Solo, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00029; Olivier (Box 13)
    - College Fest, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00030; Oliver (Box 13)
    - Maria Judge, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00031; Olivier (Box 13)
    - Mid East Conference, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00032; Newman, Stephen (Box 13)
    - Parents Weekend, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00033; Mara (Box 13)
    - Financial Aid Meeting, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00034; Sur, Matthew (Box 13)
    - Branford Marsalis, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00035; Newman, Steve (Box 13)
    - Athlete of the Week, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00036; Yudiu, Pam (Box 13)
    - Homecoming, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00037; Anderson, Christine (Box 13)
    - Jean Mayer Fireside Talk, Good Carmichael Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00038; Anderson, Christine (Box 13)
    - Rehearsal at Arena/ Homecoming Banner Making, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00039; Oliver/ G, John (Box 13)
    - Oxfam Speaker, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00040; Mara (Box 13)
    - Ronald Thornten, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00041; Yudia, Pam (Box 13)
    - Senate Meeting, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00042; B, Mike (Box 13)
    - Head of Charles, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00043; Jon (Box 13)
    - Head of Charles, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00044; P, Sofia (Box 13)
    - Positive, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00045; Oliver (Box 13)
    - Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00046; Jen (Box 13)
    - Tuck In's, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00047; Denise (Box 13)
    - Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00048; Jen (Box 13)
    - 10 Exp. For Bridge, Anderson Basement 1:30, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00049; Paul (Box 13)
    - Update Israel, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00050; Oliver (Box 13)
    - LCC, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00051 (Box 13)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00052; B, Mike (Box 13)
    - Arena Theater Music, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00053; Olivier (Box 13)
    - Masspirg Trick or Treat, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00054; Sur, Matt (Box 13)
    - Karen Vitale, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00055; Jen (Box 13)
    - Senior Night, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00056 (Box 13)
    - Phil Nee, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00057; Denise (Box 13)
    - Big Brother/ Sister, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00058; Nathalie (Box 13)
    - Symposium (EPIIC Dance), 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00059; Denise (Box 13)
    - Folk Music in Hotung, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00060; Sandberg, Mike (Box 13)
    - Arob-A-Thon, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00061; Khaitsa (Box 13)
    - Kuwaiti Ambassador + Halloween on Hill, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00062; Julio (Box 13)
    - Vera Stenhouse, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00063; Philipp, Adam (Box 13)
    - Voter Drive/ Safe Sex Talk in Hogdon, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00064; Anderson, Chris/ Zahas, Lukas (Box 13)
    - Career Fair, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00065; Miller, Lisa (Box 13)
    - Iraqi Ambassador, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00066; Newman, Steve (Box 13)
    - Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00067; Sofia (Box 13)
    - Tufts Indian Cultural Fest '90, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00068 (Box 13)
    - OEE, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00069 (Box 13)
    - Alex Trebeck, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00070; Ayotte, David (Box 13)
    - The Colored Museum, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00071; Paiter (?) (Box 13)
    - Junk, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00072 (Box 13)
    - Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00073; Mara (Box 13)
    - Christian Science Monitor/ Fluff, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00074; Sofia (Box 13)
    - Candle Light Vigil Davis Square- El Salvador, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00075; Sofia (Box 13)
    - Men's Basketball, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00076; Sklar, Howard (Box 13)
    - TCUS, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00077; K, Jen (Box 13)
    - Jumbo Pub, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00078; Julio (Box 13)
    - Youth in the South African Struggle, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00079; Grauer, Jon (Box 13)
    - Administrators, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00080; Mara (Box 13)
    - Unlabelled, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00081 (Box 13)
    - Smithereens, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00082; Mara (Box 13)
    - Slide Show on S. Africa Presented by Dave Goodman, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00083; Christine (Box 13)
    - Mayer Dancing/ Fluff/ Chris Ball, 1990; UA176.002.013.00003.00084; Mara (Box 13)
  - Sports, Fall, 1989 -- 1990; UA176.002.014.00001
    - Women's Field Hockey, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00001; Skalr, Howie (Box 14)
    - Men's Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00002; Anderson, Christie (Box 14)
    - Carruso Etc., 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00003; Julio (Box 14)
    - Volleyball, 1989; UA176.002.014.00001.00004; Graver, Jonathan (Box 14)
    - Volleyball, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00005; Schmidt, Stacey (Box 14)
    - Field Hockey, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00006; Starr, Ron (Box 14)
    - Field Hockey, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00007; Sloan, Abigail (Box 14)
    - Volleyball, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00008; Starr, Ron (Box 14)
    - Paige Lampert-athlete of the week, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00009; Julio (Box 14)
    - Women's Tennis, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00010; Starr, Ron (Box 14)
    - Women's Tennis, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00011; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Volleyball, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00012; Julio (Box 14)
    - Women's Soccer vs. Williams, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00013; Joel (Box 14)
    - Women's Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00014; Mara (Box 14)
    - Women's Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00015; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Women Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00016; Buszack, Mike (Box 14)
    - Women's Soccer and W. Soccer Coach, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00017; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Women's Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00018; Schmidt, Stacey (Box 14)
    - Women's Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00019; Skalr, Howie (Box 14)
    - Men's Cross Country, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00020; Mara (Box 14)
    - Homecoming Football, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00021; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Men's Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00022; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Men's Soccer, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00023; Howard (Box 14)
    - Women's Cross Country, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00024; Mara (Box 14)
    - Tufts Ultimate (B' Team), 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00025; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Cross country team, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00026; Sur, Matt (Box 14)
    - Football, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00027; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Action Shots of Neil Hare #12, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00028; Yudin, Pam (Box 14)
    - Football Tufts V. Williams, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00029; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Tufts V. Williams, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00030; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Field Hockey, 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00031; Buszezfex, Mike (Box 14)
    - W. Hoop (Women's Basketball), 1990; UA176.002.014.00001.00032; Oliver (Box 14)
  - Faculty, Student Trip, Spring, 1991; UA176.002.014.00002
    - San Francisco, 1991; UA176.002.014.00002.00001 (Box 14)
      No date of the month on sheet
    - Sol Gittleman at dinner, 1991; UA176.002.014.00002.00002; Sophia (Box 14)
  - Events, Spring and Fall, 1989 -- 1992; UA176.002.014.00003
    - Head of the Charles, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00001; Schatz, Karl (Box 14)
    - Nescac's X-C (Cross Country), 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00002; Schatz, Karl (Box 14)
    - Women's Soccer, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00003; Schatz, Karl (Box 14)
    - Protest; Women's Soccer, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00004 (Box 14)
    - Women's Track, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00005; Schatz, Karl (Box 14)
    - Women's Swimming, 1992; UA176.002.014.00003.00006; Sophia (Box 14)
    - Men's Soccer, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00007; Stein, Matt (Box 14)
    - Women's Tennis / Men's Soccer, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00008; Nat (Box 14)
    - Staff, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00009; J., Noah (Box 14)
    - Blue-Jam, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00010; Anni (Box 14)
    - Homecoming, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00011; Anni (Box 14)
    - Unidentifiable performance, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00012 (Box 14)
    - Group pictures, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00013; Jen (Box 14)
    - Reinvestment, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00014; R., Rebecca (Box 14)
    - (Women's) Theater, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00015; Sofia (Box 14)
    - Blood Drive West Hall, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00016; Aprhodite (Box 14)
    - Recycling, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00017; Karl (Box 14)
    - Group pictures; experiment, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00018 (Box 14)
    - Rally, 1989; UA176.002.014.00003.00019; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 14)
    - Paige Hall Fire, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00020; Karl (Box 14)
    - Media Lecture, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00021; Kaplan, Jodi (Box 14)
    - Budget MT., 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00022 (Box 14)
    - Dance Collective, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00023; Karl (Box 14)
    - De La Soul, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00024; Karl (Box 14)
    - Dark Room, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00025; Tab (Box 14)
    - Bubs & Jills & Mayer 10/24, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00026; Kaplan, Jodi (Box 14)
    - Vienna Table, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00027; Kaplan, Jodi (Box 14)
    - Fluff (Harvard Square), 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00028; Tab (Box 14)
    - Somerville Theater and Fluff, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00029; Tab (Box 14)
    - New Buildings, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00030; Jen (Box 14)
    - English Dept & Student Mt., 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00031; Tab (Box 14)
    - Weight Room, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00032; Howell, John (Box 14)
    - Concert Board, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00033; Anai (Box 14)
    - Senate, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00034; Pat (Box 14)
    - Senate Meeting with Jean, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00035; Karl (Box 14)
    - TCU Senate, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00036; Bigden, Jen (Box 14)
    - Athlete of the Week, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00037; Julie (Box 14)
    - Peace Corps; Fluff, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00038; Sofia (Box 14)
    - Pat's Film, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00039 (Box 14)
    - Jean Mayer; Fluff; Olin, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00040; Pat (Box 14)
    - Homecoming '91, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00041; Schatz, K. (Box 14)
    - Homecoming '91, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00042; Schatz, K. (Box 14)
    - Oxfam, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00043; Tab (Box 14)
    - Theatre Rehearsals: Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00044; Anni (Box 14)
    - Pound and Fluff, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00045; Tab (Box 14)
    - Fluff; People Studying; New Chaplain Steve; Bonzl, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00046; Tab (Box 14)
    - S.V. Ambassador, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00047; Tab (Box 14)
    - Chris Mikulski; Fluff, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00048; Karl (Box 14)
    - Faculty Waits on You Dinner, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00049; Julio (Box 14)
    - Homecoming; Crew, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00050; Anni (Box 14)
    - Superheroes/Blue Jam, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00051; Karl (Box 14)
    - Lecture, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00052; Karl (Box 14)
      Title from sheets
    - Fred Barnes, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00053; Mishkin, Lauren (Box 14)
    - Boston Rally, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00054; Nathalie (Box 14)
    - Protest, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00055; Healy, Pat (Box 14)
      Title from sheets; year from binder
    - Boston Rally, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00056; Healy, Patrick (Box 14)
    - Goddard War Rally, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00057; Jen (Box 14)
    - Joe Swimmer and Karl Hiycyzyn; Julian Barnes, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00058; Nat; Hilary, Gail (Box 14)
    - Josh Goldburg and Jon Bilon, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00059; Jen (Box 14)
    - TUTV, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00060; Jen (Box 14)
    - Swap, Reitman, and Fluff, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00061; Mara (Box 14)
    - Marc Pryce, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00062; Drower, Denise (Box 14)
    - Women's Self Defense Class; Fluff, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00063; Julio (Box 14)
    - ASCE Bridge, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00064; Perelman, Bruce (Box 14)
    - Teach-in; Fish Place, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00065; Julio (Box 14)
    - Olin Center; Corner College: Boston Ave, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00066; Bidgen, Jon (Box 14)
    - Peace, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00067 (Box 14)
    - Jills, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00068; Julio (Box 14)
    - Feinlieb Forum, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00069; Jen (Box 14)
    - Medford Council, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00070; Julio (Box 14)
    - Life after B.A., 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00071; Gayle (Box 14)
    - Marcia Kelley, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00072; Sofia (Box 14)
    - Fools, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00073; Karl (Box 14)
    - Dartmouth Rev., 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00074; Pezzley, Tracy; Gayle (Box 14)
    - Concrete Canoe, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00075; Jen (Box 14)
    - Photojournalism; After Hours, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00076; Nat; Jen (Box 14)
    - Medford City Council; Chicken Express, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00077; Julio (Box 14)
    - Physicians and HIV, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00078; Recordati, Anni (Box 14)
    - Trustees Luncheon, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00079; Karl (Box 14)
    - Dance Collective, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00080; Nelsons, Stefanie (Box 14)
    - TCU Senate, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00081; Graver, Jonathan (Box 14)
    - Tuftspeak, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00082; Jen (Box 14)
    - Middle East students speak out about country in turmoil, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00083; Recordati, Anni (Box 14)
    - Gott RM, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00084; Sur, Matt (Box 14)
    - Jills and Mates, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00085; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Intercultural Dance and Fashion Show, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00086; Natalie (Box 14)
    - Skippy (Marc Price), 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00087; Bidgen, Jon (Box 14)
    - Greek Jam, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00088; Jen (Box 14)
    - Greek Jam, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00089; Jen (Box 14)
    - Tuftspeak, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00090; Julio (Box 14)
    - Amos Oz, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00091; Olivier (Box 14)
    - Random portrait shots, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00092 (Box 14)
    - V.P. Candidate, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00093; Nat (Box 14)
    - Bill Shein, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00094; Sophia (Box 14)
    - ESL, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00095; Haskell, Joel (Box 14)
    - Housing Lottery, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00096; Oliver (Box 14)
    - Tuftspeak, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00097; Julio (Box 14)
    - April Fool's Tuftspeak, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00098 (Box 14)
    - Speak on Latin American Religion and the Last V.P. Candidate, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00099; Jen (Box 14)
    - Random portrait shots, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00100; Julio (Box 14)
    - Date Rape Panel, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00101; Olivier (Box 14)
    - Jessica Singal, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00102; Olivier (Box 14)
    - Senate Candidates, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00103; Jen (Box 14)
    - Senate Candidates, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00104; Jen (Box 14)
    - Senate Candidates, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00105; Jen (Box 14)
    - Porn and Ads, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00106; Olivier (Box 14)
    - Amnesty Concert, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00107 (Box 14)
    - Senate Presidential Candidates, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00108 (Box 14)
    - Academic Awards Ceremony, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00109; Anni (Box 14)
    - Rock Gym, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00110; Aprhodite (Box 14)
    - Modernism and Jazz Band, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00111; Anni (Box 14)
    - Fire and Voting, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00112; Anna (Box 14)
    - Asian AM, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00113; Julio (Box 14)
    - Amalgamates, 1991; UA176.002.014.00003.00114; Murphy, Jon (Box 14)